http://www.firefightersims.com/p/privacy-policy.html

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy for www.fireaccreditation.com If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at admin@fireaccreditation.com. At www.fireaccreditation.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.fireaccreditation.com and how it is used. Log FilesLike many other Web sites, www.fireaccreditation.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. Cookies and Web Beacons www.fireaccreditation.com does not use cookies. DoubleClick DART Cookie .:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.fireaccreditation.com..:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.fireaccreditation.com and other sites on the Internet. .:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ....Google AdsenseCommission JunctionLinkshareAmazonThese third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.fireaccreditation.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. www.fireaccreditation.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.fireaccreditation.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Share
Get link
Facebook
Twitter
Pinterest
Email
Other Apps
Share
German Fire Simulator Game
In my continuous search for fire simulators, today I came across a German PC game.
The game is called Feuerwehr Simulator 2010 .
Below is the trailer and I went to the website and used Google to translate it.
Here are the details of the game:
What Fire fans have been waiting for. The fire simulator 2010 provides for the first time a realistic fire simulation from a first person perspective of the fireman. The development studio VSTEP also stands out for professional fire simulations for firefighters.
Take on the role of one or more men of a fire station. In various scenarios, you have to fight fires or rescue people. Here you have the extensive use your equipment vehicles: tubes / pipes, axes, aerial ladder, breathing apparatus etc.
The following missions are in the simulation:
•Small fire in a locked house
•Burning gas station
•Traffic accident in tunnel
•Train accident
•Save children from a burning building
•Fire on a ship in port
•Truck accident involving hazardous
Share
Emergency's Randolph Mantooth At Fire-Rescue Med
I headed out again this year to Las Vegas for Fire-Rescue Med.
I attended last year and found it well worth the trip.
I really wanted to go again this year so I made sure I put in my training request early. I recommend EMS Personnel and Narcotics Tampering: Awareness and Prevention, interesting stuff.
I saw Randolph Mantooth at the conference last year and am looking forward to seeing him again.
Below is a nice interview with the actor by ems1.com about the conference.
AND NARCOTICS TAMPERING:
I wanted to let everyone know about a new photo site I am working on.
I was trying to think of a really great way for firefighters to share their pictures.
I am not super high tech yet so I am working on a blog and pulling pictures from across the web that I really like.
The new website I am working on is called firefighterphotos.com .
I thought is was a great name and also found a pretty good looking blog template.
Right now I am pulling in photos from across the web that allow sharing (creative commons) and posting them.
The only problem is that most of the photo sites do not have any stories that relate to the photos.
I would really like to be able to get some great stories to also post.
If anyone is looking to share some pictures or looking to get some backlinks for their fire blog or department page, send me a line.
If you have some picture that you are the owner of just email me
and I will post and hook you up with a link on my page to your site.
